<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SportsFete</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="dialog_title">Select Department</string>

    <string-array name="department_array">
        <item>ALL</item>
        <item>ARCHI</item>
        <item>CHEM</item>
        <item>CIVIL</item>
        <item>CSE</item>
        <item>DOMS</item>
        <item>ECE</item>
        <item>EEE</item>
        <item>ICE</item>
        <item>MCA</item>
        <item>MECH</item>
        <item>META</item>
        <item>M.TECH</item>
        <item>PhD/MSc/MS</item>
        <item>PROD</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sport_array">
        <item>Athletics</item>
        <item>Badminton(Mixed)</item>
        <item>Basketball(Boys)</item>
        <item>Basketball(Girls)</item>
        <item>Carrom</item>
        <item>Chess</item>
        <item>Cricket(Boys)</item>
        <item>Cricket(Girls)</item>
        <item>Football(Boys)</item>
        <item>Football(Girls)</item>
        <item>Handball(Boys)</item>
        <item>Handball(Girls)</item>
        <item>Hockey(Boys)</item>
        <item>Kabaddi</item>
        <item>Kho Kho(Boys)</item>
        <item>Kho Kho(Girls)</item>
        <item>Marathon</item>
        <item>Power Lifting</item>
        <item>Swimming</item>
        <item>Table Tennis(Boys)</item>
        <item>Table Tennis(Girls)</item>
        <item>Tennis(Boys)</item>
        <item>Tennis(Girls)</item>
        <item>Throwball</item>
        <item>Volley Ball(Boys)</item>
        <item>Volley Ball(Girls)</item>
        <item>Water Polo</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="department_array_shared_preference">
        <item>ARCHI</item>
        <item>CHEM</item>
        <item>CIVIL</item>
        <item>CSE</item>
        <item>DOMS</item>
        <item>ECE</item>
        <item>EEE</item>
        <item>ICE</item>
        <item>MCA</item>
        <item>MECH</item>
        <item>META</item>
        <item>M_TECH</item>
        <item>PHD_MSC_MS</item>
        <item>PROD</item>
    </string-array>

 <string name="Athletics">
        <![CDATA[
 <b>
            <p>INDIVIDUAL:- <br>
                            &emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 5 points<br>
                            &emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 3 points<br>
                            &emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 1 point<br>
            </p>
            <p>
                            RELAY:-
                            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 10 points
                            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd- 6 points
                            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd- 4 points</b>
            </p>


            <p>MEN’S EVENTS-100m, 200m, 400m, 800m, 1500m, 5000m, 4*100 relay, 4*400 relay.
            Long Jump, High Jump, Triple Jump, Shotput, Discuss Throw, Javelin
            Throw and Mixed Relay.</p>

            <p>GIRL’S EVENTS-
            100m, 200m, 400m, 800m, 1500m, 4*100 relay, 4 *400 relay
            Long Jump, High Jump, Shotput and Discuss Throw and Mixed Relay.:</p>
            <p>Rules:
                <ul class="rules">
                <li>For each event, only 2 participants can take part from each department.</li>
                <li>A minimum of 5 different departments must be there for each event to take place.</li>
                <li>A participant can take part in maximum of 4 events excluding relay (maximum of 2 field and 2 track events or vice versa).</li>
                <li>Standard IAAF rules apply.</li>


                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Ahmed Hasan :9994699175(Boys)</p>
                   <p>Pragya Rai: 9487730851(Girls)</p>

            </p>
    ]]>

    </string>

    <string name="Badminton">
    <![CDATA[
<b>
            <p>POINTS:-
               <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 20 points
               <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 12 points
               <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 8 points</b>
            </p>




            <p>Rules:
                <ul class="rules">
                <li>Only 1 team per department.</li>
                <li>Each team should have minimum of 2 boys and 2 girls and maximum of 4 boys and 4 girls.</li>
                <li>The tournament is conducted on a knockout basis.</li>
                <li>The order of play for each match will be:<br>
                    i) Boys Singles  <br>
                    ii) Girls Singles <br>
                    iii) Mixed Doubles <br>
                    iv) Girls Doubles <br>
                    v) Boys Doubles <br>
                    Team should secure 3 out of 5 games to win the match.</li>

               <li>The order of play can be changed only if both the departments are willing to change.</li>
                <li>Each game will be played for best for 3 sets and each set will be played for 15 points. Finals alone will be best of 3 sets for 21 points. </li>
                <li>All rounds will be played in plastic shuttles. </li>
                <li>Umpire’s decision is final in any dispute (point, line judgement, faults etc....).</li>
                <li>Standard BWF rules apply.</li>

                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Roshan Joseph: 9940866409 </p>

            </p>

           ]]>

    </string>

    <string name="Basketball">
            <![CDATA[

            <h3>Basketball(Boys)</h3>
            <p>
                POINTS:-<br><b>
                &emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 20 points<br>
               &emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 12 points<br>
               &emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 8 points</b>
            </p>
            <p>
                GAME TIME:<br>

                &emsp;4 Quarters of 10 minutes each.<br>
                &emsp;1 Timeout per quarter till third quarter, 2 Timeouts in the fourth quarter.<br>
                &emsp;Side change is mandatory after the first half.<br>
            </p>
            <p>Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Each round is knockout based.</li>
                <li>A team can have a maximum of 12 players.</li>
                <li>A maximum of 5 personal fouls per player will be allowed per game.</li>
                <li>A player receiving 2 technical fouls shall be replaced immediately and will not be allowed to take part any further in that tie.</li>
                <li>Every foul after 5 team fouls in a quarter will results in 2 free throws.</li>
                <li>A technical foul will result in two free throws to the opposite team in open court.</li>
                <li>All the violations will be judged according to FIBA rules and regulations.</li>
                <li>Referee’s decision is final.</li>



            </ul>

            </p>

            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Ninada Ashok: 9790483112 </p>

            </p><br>


   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Basketball_Girls">

        <![CDATA[

        <h3>Basketball(girls)</h3>

             <p>
                POINTS:- <b>
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 12 points
               <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 8 points
               <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 5 points</b>

            </p>
            <p>
                GAME TIME:<br>

                League matches - 8 minute per half, half break – 2 mins<br>
                Quarters, Semis and Final matches – 6 min per quarter, half break – 2 mins<br>
                Each team is allowed one 45 second time out per quarter/ half.
            </p>
            <p>Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Each round is knockout based.</li>
                <li>Size 6 basketball will be used.</li>
                <li>3 main players and 2 substitute players are allowed per team.</li>
                <li>There will be no jump ball.</li>
                <li>No free throws on fouling; the ball is awarded to the fouled team.</li>
                <li>Each team will be given 5 team fouls before free throw attempts are awarded. Upon the 6th team foul, the fouled player will shoot one free throw.</li>
                <li>Each player will be given 3 personal fouls before she is made to leave court. That player is not allowed to participate in the game. A substitute may be called on.</li>
                <li>All the violations will be judged according to FIBA rules and regulations.</li>
                <li>Referee’s decision is final.</li>
                <li>NOTE: All the matches will be conducted in half court only.</li>

            </ul>

            </p>
            <p>General Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Baskets are scored in 2’s and 3’s Winner’s ball after every conversion.</li>
                <li>The ball must be either passed or brought in after clearing from half court line.</li>
                <li>Afterr any change of possession, the ball should be cleared past the 3 point line Instead of side line passes; a player may also bring the ball in herself after checking it with the opposing team.</li>
                <li>After each free throw attempt, make or miss, the non-shooting team will receive the ball at the half court line.</li>
                <li>A ball out of bounds will be taken out from the half court line by the opposite team. </li>
                <li>5 second rule: A player must complete a side line pass within 5 seconds. Else ball possession is awarded to opposite team.</li>


            </ul>

            </p>
             <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Ridhima Pebbisetty: 9597311801 </p>

            </p>

        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Carrom">
            <![CDATA[
    <p>
                POINTS:-<b>
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 15 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 10 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 6 points</b>
            </p>

            <p>Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Thumbing is allowed.</li>
                <li>National carrom rules will be followed.</li>
                <li>Each department will consist of one pair of girls’ team and two pairs of boys’ team. (Total – 4 boys, 2 girls).</li>
                <li>Each pair will play best of three matches. If two of the three pairs win,
                    then that department will win that tie.</li>
                <li>Strikers and coins will be provided. Each player is also allowed to bring his own striker.</li>

            </ul>

            </p>
            <p>Game Format:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>First round will be of knock out. The winners of the knock out round will advance to the double elimination format.</li>
                <li>Only finals will be of points format. Each team from a department will play for 21 points. Red/queen value is 3 points. The team which reaches 21 points first wins that round.</li>
                <li>NOTE: For each strike, 30-sec time limit for positioning the striker.</li>

            </ul>

            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Rahitya Rongali: 9790064258</p>

            </p>

   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Chess">
            <![CDATA[
    <p>
                POINTS:-<b>
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place- 15 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place- 10 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place- 6 points </b>
            </p>

            <p>Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Tournament will be conducted on a Swiss – System format.</li>
                <li>Each team comprises of five players. (Boys/Girls).<br> (Minimum of 2 girls per team)</li>
                <li>Time Control: 30 min + 15 sec increment for each move.</li>
                <li>Walk over time 15 min. Inform the arbiter and opposing captain beforehand if a player will arrive late for the game.</li>
                <li>Players are requested to bring their own CHESS SETS.</li>
                <li>All FIDE rules will be followed.</li>
                <li>Arbiter’s decision is final.</li>

            </ul>

            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Siddarth:9840954969</p>

            </p>

   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Cricket">
            <![CDATA[

            <h3>Cricket(Boys)</h3>
  <p>
                POINTS:- <b>
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 25 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 18 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 12 points </b>
            </p>

            <p>Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>All ICC rules to be followed.</li>
                <li>Each team should consist of 11 players (+4 sub). Each innings is of 12 overs. 3rd place and Finals will be a 15 over game.</li>
                <li>Matches will be played with a cricket ball (leather ball) and a new ball will be given for each match based on availability.</li>
                <li>Compulsory whites (white tee and white track) to be worn by all players including substitutes.</li>
                <li>Shoes are compulsory.</li>
                <li>All standard international rules apply (example decisions regarding lbw and no-ball are there).</li>
                <li>1st 3 overs-mandatory power play. NO SUBSEQUENT POWERPLAYS. Only two fielders allowed outside the ring during power play. For the 3rd place and finals the first five overs will be power play.</li>
                <li>No-ball to be awarded if any player of the fielding team speaks or cheers during ball being bowled.</li>
                <li>Umpire’s decision is final.</li>
                <li>Time limit for the respective no. of overs :-<br>

                12 overs -50 mins<br>
                15 overs - 60 mins<br>
                </li>
                <li>Penalty of runs or reducing the number of overs to be bowled for
                    exceeding time limit.</li>
            </ul>
        </p>
        <p>

            <b>Note for all the captains:-</b><br>
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>The decision of the umpire will be final and any form of violation in terms of arguments with the umpire will eventually lead to the disqualification of the team.</li>
                <li>Teams should report at the given time on the field, failing to do so will lead to the disqualification of the team.</li>
                <li>All cricket equipment need to be used with care. Damaging of equipment will be dealt with serious consequences.</li>
                <li>Any other queries can be made with the event coordinator and only them. Information regarding fixtures and groups cannot be questioned.</li>
                <li>The schedule of their respective games shall be informed in advance and hence all players from the respective teams must arrive at least half an hour prior to each game.</li>
                <li>Matches should be played in the spirit of the game.</li>

            </ul>

        </p>
        <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Kaushik: 8105841034</p>


            </p><br>

   ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="Cricket_Girls">
            <![CDATA[

            <h3>Cricket(Girls)</h3>
            <p>
                <b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 15 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 8 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 5 points</b>
            </p>

            <p>Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Tournament is conducted on Knockout basis.</li>
                <li>6 girls per side (+1 sub). Sub allowed only when any player is injured.
                6 overs per innings.</li>
                <li>In 6 overs match minimum of 3 bowlers to be used.</li>
                <li>Final alone would be of 8 over where minimum 4 bowlers to be used.</li>
                <li>1 run for wide and no ball. Extras only for wide and no-balls. Overthrow is there.</li>
                <li>Free hit for the ball delivered after no ball.</li>
                <li>You can either chuck the ball or bowl. No under arm bowling.</li>
                <li>Full toss above the waist is a no ball.</li>
                <li>No runs behind the stumps other than boundary.</li>
                <li>No runs for leg-bye, bye. No lbw dismissals.</li>
                <li>No fielder allowed to stand behind the bowler before the ball is delivered.</li>
                <li>Cosco ball would be used.</li>
                <li>Penalty of runs for exceeding time limit.</li>
            </ul>
        </p>
        <p>

            <b>Note for all the captains:-</b><br>
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>The decision of the umpire will be final and any form of violation in terms of arguments with the umpire will eventually lead to the disqualification of the team.</li>
                <li>Teams should report at the given time on the field, failing to do so will lead to the disqualification of the team.</li>
                <li>If the team didn’t turn up for the match, then it is taken as loss of
                     match for them and other team will be rewarded the winning points.</li>
                <li>Except the captains, no other member (maybe a team members or
                    team management or coach) has the right to have discussion with the
                    umpire regarding any decision made by the umpire and any violation
                    of this rule will eventually lead to the disqualification of the team.</li>

            </ul>

        </p>
        <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Kaushik: 8105841034</p>


        </p>

   ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="Football">
            <![CDATA[
                        <h3>Football(Boys)</h3>
  <p>
                <b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 25 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 18 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 12 points </b>
            </p>

            <p>Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>League cum knockout format.</li>
                <li>Each group match will have a half time of 20 minutes.</li>
                <li>Knockout phase will have a half time of 25 minutes.</li>
                <li>If a group match ends in a draw, the points will be split.</li>
                <li>If a knockout match ends in a draw, match proceeds to Penalties
                    (No Extra Time).</li>
                <li>Any match deemed a WALKOVER, the winning team will get 3 points and plus 3 goals. (Losing team gets No points and minus 3 goals.)</li>
                <li>Positions within the Leagues will be calculated by:
                • Number of points.<br>
                • Goal difference.<br>
                • Goals scored.<br>
                </li>
                <li>If there is still a tie between two teams then the result will be declared by a coin toss.</li>
                <li>If a knockout match ends in a draw, match proceeds to Penalties(No Extra Time).</li>
                <li>Winners of each group proceed to the knockout stage.</li>
                <li>Maximum of 16 players per department.</li>
                <li>Rolling substitutions are allowed.</li>
                <li>Teams are expected to report 10 minutes before the start of each match.Any team that reports late or not coming without prior information will be
                   will be awarded negative points.</li>
                <li>The Referee’s decision is final and abiding.</li>
                <li>Foul language or fighting will not be entertained. Strict action will be
                    taken against the team involved in any of these acts.</li>
                <li>All other standard rules apply.</li>

            </ul>

            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Uzair Iqbal :9790487713</p>


            </p><br>

   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Football_Girls">
            <![CDATA[

            <h3>Football(Girls)</h3>
            <p>
                <b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 15 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 8 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 5 points</b>
            </p>

            <p>Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Each round is knockout based.</li>
                <li>Matches excluding the finals will have a half-length of 8 mins.</li>
                <li>The finals will have a half-length of 10 mins.</li>
                <li>If a knockout match ends in a draw, the match will proceed directly to penalty shootouts. (There will be no extra-time)</li>
                <li>Each team can have a maximum of 8 players with 5 players taking the field including a goal keeper.</li>
                <li>Rolling substitutions are allowed.</li>
                <li>Teams are requested to be there in the ground 10 minutes before the start of their match.Any team that reports late or not coming without
                    prior information will be awarded negative points.</li>
                <li>The Referee’s decision is final and abiding.</li>
                <li>Foul language or fighting will not be entertained. Strict action will be
                    taken against the team involved in any of these acts.</li>
                <li>All other standard rules apply.</li>


            </ul>

            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Uzair Iqbal :9790487713</p>


            </p>

   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Handball_Boys">
            <![CDATA[
 <p>
                <b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 20 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 12 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 8 points</b>
            </p>

            <p>Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Tournament is conducted on a knock out basis.</li>
                <li>Number of players = 6+1 (+5 subs)</li>
                <li>Two halves with each half 20 mins (though final timing decision is in the hands of referee)</li>
                <li>IHF rules/fouls of double dribble, carry, 3 second hold, walk, line cut applies along with passive play and aggression.</li>
                <li>Decisions of free throw, 7-meter penalty, corner in and throw in rests on referee.</li>
                <li>The final decision is made by the field referee which must strictly be adhered to.</li>
                <li>All the players should wear sports shoes. Being barefoot and wearing boots and spikes are not allowed.</li>
                <li>All the players must cut their nails properly before the game starts.</li>
                <li>All the players should wear shorts. Track pants and jeans are not allowed.</li>
                <li>The Goal Keeper can wear track pants.</li>
                <li>If the match ends in a tie, 5 minutes’ extra time (maximum twice). If it’s still a tie, the outcome of the match will be decided by penalty shoot-out.</li>
                <li>Arguing with the referees, fighting with other team players and late
                  reporting without prior information will lead to disqualification of the
                    team.</li>


            </ul>

            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Chaitanya:9790065834</p>


            </p>

   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Handball_Girls">
            <![CDATA[
 <p>
                <b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 15 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 12 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 8 points</b>
            </p>

            <p>Rules:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Tournament is conducted on a knock out basis.</li>
                <li>Number of players = 6+1 (+5 subs)</li>
                <li>Two halves with each half 20 mins (though final timing decision is in the hands of referee)</li>
                <li>IHF rules/fouls of double dribble, carry, 3 second hold, walk, line cut applies along with passive play and aggression.</li>
                <li>Decisions of free throw, 7-meter penalty, corner in and throw in rests on referee.</li>
                <li>The final decision is made by the field referee which must strictly be adhered to.</li>
                <li>All the players should wear sports shoes. Being barefoot and wearing boots and spikes are not allowed.</li>
                <li>All the players should wear shorts or track pants and jeans are notallowed.</li>
                <li>The Goal Keeper can wear track pants.</li>
                <li>All the players must cut their nails properly before the game starts.</li>
                <li>If the match ends in a tie, 5 minutes’ extra time (maximum twice). If it’s still a tie, the outcome of the match will be decided by penalty shoot-out.</li>
                <li>Arguing with the referees, fighting with other team players and late
                   reporting without prior information will lead to disqualification of the
                    team.</li>


            </ul>

            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Chaitanya:9790065834</p>


            </p>

   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Hockey">
            <![CDATA[
  <p>
                <b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 20 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 12 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 8 points</b>
            </p>

            <p>
                TEAM:-<br>
            A Team consists of maximum 7 players composed of maximum 5
            players on field and up to 2 substitutes.
            </p>

            <p>RULES:-
             <ul class="rules">
                <li>Match time of 15 mins during the knockout stages for each halves. Half time interval of 5 mins.</li>
                <li>Match time of 20 mins during the semifinal and final match for each halves.</li>
                <li> Halftime interval of 8 mins</li>
                <li>Goals are scored once it clears the goal line and should be inside the “D” line.</li>
                <li>Centre start at the start of play. And sideline start for foul play.</li>
                <li>Passes and shots should be strictly either push or tap, other means will be considered as foul.</li>
                <li>Rolling substitutions are allowed.</li>
                <li>If a knockout match ends in a draw, match proceeds to Penalties.</li>
                <li>The Penalty stroke will start from center line.</li>
            </ul>
            </p>
            <p>Fouls and Violations:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Scoops, Flick and Hit will be considered as foul.</li>
                <li>Dangerous play can be booked and the player can be seated out up to 2 mins.</li>
                <li>Other violations in accordance to FIH rules will apply.</li>
            </ul>
            </p>
            <p>Play:
            <ul class="rules">
                <li>Matches will be held at Hockey Ground located near CCD.</li>
                <li>Teams are expected to report 10 minutes before the start of each match.</li>





            </ul>

            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Himanshu Mewara :9413903714</p>


            </p>
   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Kabaddi">
            <![CDATA[
  <p>
                <p> <b>POINTS:-
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 20 points
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 12 points
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 8 points </b>
            </p>
            <p>RULES:-
                <ul class="rules">
                    <li>Tournament is conducted on a knockout basis.</li>
                    <li>Each team shall consist of maximum of 12 players and 7 Players shall take the ground at a time and the remaining players are substitutes.</li>
                    <li>Duration of the match: Match shall be two halves of 15 minutes with 5 minutes interval.</li>
                    <li>The teams will change court after interval.</li>
                    <li>TThe number of players for each team in the court at the start of second half shall remain the same as it was at the end of first half.
                    </li>
                    <li>NOTE: The last raid of each half of the match shall be allowed to be completed even after completion of the scheduled time as mentioned above.</li>
                    <li>Each team shall score one point for every opponent out or put out. The side, which scores a LONA, shall score two extra points</li>
                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>Time out:
                <ul class="rules">
                    <li>Each Team shall be allowed to take Two “Time Outs” of 30 Seconds each in each half; such time out shall be called for by the Captain or any playing member of the team with the permission of referee. The time out time shall be added to match time. </li>
                    <li>During the time out the teams shall not leave the ground, any violation in this; a technical point shall be awarded to the opponent team
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>Bonus Point:
                <ul class="rules">
                    <li>One point shall be awarded to the raider when he crosses the bonus line. If the raider after crossing the bonus line is caught, the opponent team is awarded one point.</li>
                    <li>The Bonus line will be applicable when there are minimum 6 players in the court.</li>
                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>Super Tackle
                <ul class="rules">
                    <li>Super tackle is specific scenario where a rider from the opponent team has to be tackled or caught by either 3 or less than 3 players of the defending team. In case of super tackle, the defending team will be awarded with two points.</li>
                    <li>Referee’s decision is final.</li>
                    <li>NOTE: No Do - or - Die raids, all other standard rules apply.</li>
                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>Venkateswarlu :9487731437</p>
            </p>
   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="KhoKho">
            <![CDATA[

                       <h3>Kho-Kho(Boys)</h3>
  <p><b>POINTS:-
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 20 points
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 12 points
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 8 points </b>

            <p>RULES:-
                <ul class="rules">
                    <li>Each team consists of 12 players, 9 players take the field, 3 substitutes.</li>
                    <li>A match consists of two innings. An innings consists of chasing and
                        running turns of 6 minutes each for league stages and 7 minutes each
                        for semifinals and finals.</li>
                    <li>5 minutes break for each innings. </li>
                    <li>1 team sits/kneels in the middle of the court, in a row, with adjacent members facing opposite directions.</li>
                    <li>The chasers end in the shortest time possible.</li>
                    <li>The team that takes the shortest time to tag/tap all the opponents in the field wins.</li>
                    <li>Players must sit in a zig-zag manner.</li>
                    <li>Any team that reports late by half an hour or more without prior
information will be disqualified and opponent will be judged as winners.</li>
                    <li>Umpires decision is final in any dispute (faults, point, judgements).</li>
                    <li>Runners shouldn’t touch chasers(Intentionally). Warning will be given for
two times. If runner repeats, he will be given out.</li>
                    <li>In case of walkover, opponent team will be declared as winners with 9
points difference.</li>


                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Naveen Maloth : 9677949627</p>
            </p><br>

   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="KhoKho_Girls">
            <![CDATA[

            <h3>Kho-Kho(Girls)</h3>
            <p><b>POINTS:-
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 15 points
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 10 points
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 6 points</b>
            </p>
            <p>RULES:-
                <ul class="rules">
                    <li>Each team consists of 12 players, 9 players take the field, 3 substitutes.</li>
                    <li>A match consists of two innings. An innings consists of chasing and
                        running turns of 6 minutes each for league stages and 7 minutes each
                        for semifinals and finals.</li>
                    <li>5 minutes break for each innings. </li>
                    <li>1 team sits/kneels in the middle of the court, in a row, with adjacent members facing opposite directions.</li>
                    <li>The chasers end in the shortest time possible.</li>
                    <li>The team that takes the shortest time to tag/tap all the opponents in the field wins.</li>
                    <li>Players must sit in a zig-zag manner.</li>
                    <li>Any team that reports late by half an hour or more without prior
information will be disqualified and opponent will be judged as winners.</li>
                    <li>Umpires decision is final in any dispute (faults, point, judgements).</li>
                    <li>Runners shouldn’t touch chasers(Intentionally). Warning will be given for
two times. If runner repeats, he will be given out.</li>
                    <li>In case of walkover, opponent team will be declared as winners with 9
points difference.</li>


                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Shankuntala Done: 9629915655</p>
            </p>
   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Marathon">
            <![CDATA[
  <p><b>POINTS (Men):-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 12 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 8 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 5 points </b>
                </p>
                <p><b>POINTS (Women):-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 10 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 6 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 4 points</b>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                    <ul class="rules">
                        <li>Girls need to complete 3 rounds i.e., about 6 km and within a time limit of 1.5 times the first girl who completes and will be awarded 1 point.</li>
                        <li>Boys need to complete 3 rounds i.e., about 10 km and within a time limit of 1.5 times the first boy who completes and will be awarded 1 point.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>CIRCUIT: -
                   <p> BOYS-</p>
                    <p>PD OFFICE – LIBRARY – HOSPITAL – ZIRCON BACKSIDE  – AMBER – MEGA MESS 2 – GARNET – ORION –CHEMICAL DEPT – PD OFFICE.</p>

                    <p>GIRLS-</p>
                    <p>PD OFFICE - LIBRARY- SHOPPING COMPLEX - BERY HOSTEL - AGATE HOSTEL – ORION - CHEMICAL DEPT – PD OFFICE

                </p>

   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="MrNITT">
            <![CDATA[
  <p><b>POINTS:-
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 20 points
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 12 points
            <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 8 points </b>

            <p>RULES:-
                <ul class="rules">
                    <li>First round will be Knock out. The winners will advance to league stage.</li>
                    <li>Each team consists of 12 players, 9 players take the field, 3 substitutes.</li>
                    <li>A match consists of four innings. An innings consists of chasing or running turns of 7 minutes each.</li>
                    <li>The duration of first and third innings break is 5 minutes. The duration of second innings break is 7 minutes. </li>
                    <li>1 team sits/kneels in the middle of the court, in a row, with adjacent members facing opposite directions.</li>
                    <li>The chasers end in the shortest time possible.</li>
                    <li>The team that takes the shortest time to tag/tap all the opponents in the field wins.</li>
                    <li>Players must sit in a zig-zag manner.</li>
                    <li>Referee’s decision is final. </li>
                    <li>Other standard A.K.K.F. rules apply.</li>

                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Bibek : 8122349537</p>
            </p>
   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="PowerLifting">
            <![CDATA[
   <p><b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 7 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 3 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 1 point</b>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <ul class="rules">
                        <li>&lt;56 kg</li>
                        <li>&lt;62 kg</li>
                        <li>&lt;69 kg</li>
                        <li>&lt;77 kg</li>
                        <li>&lt;85 kg</li>
                        <li>85+ kg</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                <p>The competition will be held as per the International Powerlifting
                    Federation Rules unless otherwise modified.</p>
                <p>Athletes in the sport are divided in six weight classes and placing is
                    based on the total weight lifted on the three main lifts:</p>
                <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;A. Squats</p>
                <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;B. Bench Press</p>
                <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;C. Deadlift</p>
                    <ul class="rules">
                        <li>From each Department Only 2 participants would be allowed per
                             category.</li>
                        <li>For an event to take place, minimum 5 different Departments should
                            register the event.</li>
                        <li>During the weighing of athlete, he must mention his first lift for squat
                          (minimum 50kg), bench-press(minimum 40kg) and deadlift(minimum
                           70kg) to referee.</li>
                        <li>Each competitor is allowed three attempts on each lift. The lifter’s best
                            valid attempt on each lift counts toward his competition total.</li>
                        <li>Once the highest value has been collected for each lift, the total weight
                           lifted in squat, bench press and deadlift added up. The lifter with the
                           highest combined weight lifted becomes the champion. In the case of a
                           tie, the lifter whose body weight is less becomes the champion.</li>
                        <li>Player must come with proper kit during competition and Gloves are not
                             allowed.</li>
                        <li>A player can participate in only one category.</li>
                        <li>In case of any controversy during competition and weighing, judge’s
                               decision will consider as final decision.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>General Rules for Squats:</p>
                <p>The lifter must Squat down until their hip joint is lower than their knee joint,failure to which, will lead to disqualification of that lift.</p>
                <p>General Rules for Bench Press:</p>
                <p>The bar is to be lowered to the chest area until it touches the chest and then raised, failure of which will lead to disqualification.</p>
                <p>General Rules for Deadlift:</p>
                <p>As soon as you lift the bar, set your shoulders back and ensure your kneesare locked out. Any downward movement of the bar before it reaches thefinal position will lead to disqualification.</p>
                <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Shiroya Vivek : 9790484626</p>
                </p>
   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Swimming">
            <![CDATA[
  <p>POINTS:-
                <p><b>INDIVIDUAL:
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 5 points
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 3 points
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 1 point
                <br>RELAY:
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 10 points
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 6 points
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 4 points
                <br>INDIVIDUAL (for 25m individual events only):
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place – 2.5 points
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place – 1.5 points
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place – 0.5 point
                <br>RELAY (for 4x25m freestyle relay only):
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 5 points
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 3 points
                      <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 1 points </b></p>
                <p>MEN’S EVENTS:-</p>
                   <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Freestyle: 50m, 100m, 200m.</p>
                    <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Back stroke: 50m, 100m.</p>
                    <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Breast stroke: 50m, 100m.</p>
                    <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Butterfly: 25m, 50m.</p>
                    <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Individual Medley: 100m.</p>
                   <p> &emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Relay: 4*50m freestyle, 4*25m medley relay.</p>
                <p>WOMEN\'S EVENTS:-</p>
                    <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Freestyle: 25m, 50m, 100m.</p>
                    <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Back stroke: 25m, 50m</p>
                    <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Breast stroke: 25m, 50m.</p>
                    <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Butterfly: 25m, 50m.</p>
                    <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Individual Medley: 100m.</p>
                    <p>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;Relay: 4*25m freestyle, 4*50m freestyle, 4*25m medley relay</p>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                    <ul class="rules">
                        <li>For each event, at most 2 participants can take part from each department.</li>
                        <li>Participants from a minimum of
                        <br>a) 5 different departments for men’s events
                        <br>b) 4 different departments for women’s events must be there for each event to take place, else event to be scrapped.</li>
                        <li>A participant can take part in a maximum of 3 events excluding Individual Medley and relays.</li>
                        <li>All events will be conducted on a time trial basis only. (NO heats and finals process)</li>
                        <li>All participants shall bring their own swimming gear. The Swimming gear will not be provided to them by the organizers.</li>
                        <li>Participants should report to the venue on time. The events will happen as scheduled and late comers will not be given a second chance to participate in the events they had missed.</li>
                        <li>Events will be conducted only once.</li>
                        <li>Standard FINA rules apply.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Esun Selvam : 9940222566</p>
                    <p>Dhakshaayani : 9486580217</p>
                </p>
   ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="TableTennis">
            <![CDATA[
  <p><b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 10 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 6 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 4 points</b>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                    <ul class="rules">
                         <li>Each team must have a minimum of 2 boys.</li>
                         <li>The first round matches will be for Best of 3.</li>
                         <li>From quarters, the matches will be for Best of 5.</li>
                        <li>All matches will be decided on best of 5 sets.</li>
                        <li>Match order:
                        <br>1. Singles boys

                        <br>2. Doubles boys
                        <br>3. Singles boys</li>
                        <li>Each player can play maximum 2 matches (i.e., one singles and one doubles but not two singles).</li>
                        <li>All ITTF rules are applicable.</li>
                        <li>Report 15 minutes prior to the scheduled time.</li>
                        <li>If the respective team does not report for its match as per the schedule the opponent team will get a walk-over.</li>
                        <li>All the participants are requested to bring their own bats but the balls will be provided by the organizers for all the matches.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Kanha Sodani : 9460327981</p>
                </p>
   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="TableTennis_girls">
            <![CDATA[
  <p><b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 7 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 5 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 3 points</b>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                    <ul class="rules">
                         <li>Each department can send max 2 girl players</li>
                         <li>Girls Singles is the only event.</li>
                         <li>In the initial rounds, the matches will be for Best of 3.</li>
                         <li>From quarters, the matches will be for Best of 5.</li>
                        <li>Umpire decision will be final.</li>
                        <li>All ITTF rules are applicable.</li>
                        <li>Report 15 minutes prior to the scheduled time.</li>
                        <li>If the respective team does not report for its match as per the schedule the opponent team will get a walk-over.</li>
                        <li>All the participants are requested to bring their own bats but the balls will be provided by the organizers for all the matches.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Kanha Sodani : 9460327981</p>
                </p>
   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Tennis">
            <![CDATA[
                            <h3>Tennis (MEN)</h3>
  <p><b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 12 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 8 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 5 points</b>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                    <ul class="rules">
                        <li>Maximum of two teams can register per department.</li>
                        <li>Minimum of two players and maximum of four players per team. </li>
                        <li>Three matches will be played in the order of 1st singles, doubles, 2nd
                            singles. </li>
                        <li>The team which wins two matches qualifies to the next round.</li>
                        <li>A player can play a maximum of two matches (a singles and a doubles).</li>
                        <li>All matches will be conducted on knockout basis. </li>
                        <li>All matches till (including) quarter-finals will be played best of 13 games (6-all, tiebreak). </li>
                        <li>Semi-finals for boys will be best of 17 games (8-all tie breaker).</li>
                        <li>Final: best 19 games (9-all tie breaker).</li>
                        <li>Standard International Tennis Federation (ITF) rules apply.</li>
                        <li>The referee’s decision will be final. Teams not adhering to the rules and regulations will be disqualified from the event.</li>
                        <li>Tennis balls will be provided. The players are requested to bring their own accessories and equipment.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Hariharan Jayakumar: 9003103462</p>
                    <p>Kousik R: 9710097997</p>
                </p><br>

   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Tennis_Girls">
            <![CDATA[

                 <h3>Tennis (WOMEN)</h3>
                <p><b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 10 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 6 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 4 points</b>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                    <ul class="rules">
                        <li>Only singles will be conducted. The team which wins the match qualifiesto the next round.</li>
                        <li>A maximum of two teams from a department is allowed in a team.</li>
                        <liAll matches conducted will be conducted on knockout basis.</li>
                        <li>All Matches will be played best of 15 games (7-all tiebreak).</li>
                        <li>Standard International Tennis Federation (ITF)  rules apply. </li>
                        <li>The referee’s decision will be final. Teams not adhering to the rules and regulations will be disqualified from the event. </li>
                        <li>Tennis balls will be provided. The players have to bring their own accessories and equipment.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Hariharan Jayakumar: 9003103462</p>
                    <p>Kousik R: 9710097997</p>
                </p><br>
   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Throwball">
            <![CDATA[
 <p><b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 15 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 10 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 6 points </b>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                    <ul class="rules">
                        <li>The tournament will be conducted on a knockout basis.</li>
                        <li>Each team will consist of 6 active players and 4 substitutes.</li>
                        <li>Rotation is mandatory.</li>
                        <li>Any ball after catching should be released within 3 seconds.</li>
                        <li>During the service, the ball cannot touch the net.</li>
                        <li>Service must be done within 8 seconds of referee’s whistle, or else the serve will be passed, and point will be awarded to the opponent.</li>
                        <li>Service should cross the front line of the other team.</li>
                        <li>Players cannot touch the net during the play but the ball can touch the net.</li>
                        <li>During catching or releasing, the ball should not touch any part of the body except the palm.</li>
                        <li>2 players cannot catch the ball at the same time.</li>
                        <li>Shifting the ball from right to left or left to right or deliberately pushing is not permitted.</li>
                        <li>Jump and throw is allowed but jump and catch is not allowed.</li>
                        <li>Double touch (juggling the ball in both hands) is not allowed while receiving the service ball.</li>
                        <li>Timeouts 2 per match and 30 seconds duration for each.</li>
                        <li>First two sets 25 points each and last set 15 points.</li>
                        <li>Teams can substitute only when it is their turn to serve; only exception is if a player gets injured. Only 1 person can be substituted at a time up to a maximum of 3 substitutes per set.</li>
                        <li>Referee’s decision is final and any appeal or argument against it will not be entertained.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Manasvi Surasani : 7032910997/p>
                </p>
   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Volleyball">
            <![CDATA[
                            <h3>VolleyBall (Boys)</h3>
  <p><b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 20 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 12 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 8 points</b>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                    <ul class="rules">
                        <li>The tournament will be conducted on a knockout basis.</li>
                        <li>A team may consist of minimum six players and maximum twelve players.</li>
                        <li>Each game will be minimum of 3 sets except the semi-final and final of 5 sets.</li>
                        <li>Each set will be of 25 points and the deciding set of 15 points.</li>
                        <li>Rotation is not mandatory. Players can switch places amongst themselves any time they want.</li>
                        <li>Time outs – 2 per set and 30 sec duration for each.</li>
                        <li>At least 3 people from a team should serve and the same player cannot continue serving once it is broken.</li>
                        <li>Service must be done within 8 seconds of referee’s whistle, or else the serve will be passed, and point will be awarded to the opponent.</li>
                        <li>All other standard rules of volleyball as per FIVB are to be followed.</li>
                        <li>Referee’s decision is final and any appeal or argument against it will not be entertained.</li>
                        <li>Report at the venue 15 minutes prior to the scheduled time.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>CONTACT :
                   <p>T.J.Dhivyabhaarath : 9489129471</p>
                </p><br>


   ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="Volleyball_Girls">
            <![CDATA[

                 <h3>VolleyBall (Girls)</h3>
                <p><b>POINTS:-
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 15 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 10 points
                <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 6 points</b>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                    <ul class="rules">
                        <li>The tournament will be conducted on a knockout basis.</l>
                        <li>A team may consist of minimum six players and maximum twelve players.</li>
                        <li>No more than 2 substitutions in a single set.</li>
                        <li>Rotation is not mandatory. Players can switch places amongst themselves any time they want.</li>
                        <li>Time outs – 2 per match and 30 sec duration for each.</li>
                        <li>All the matches will be best of three sets.</li>
                        <li>First two sets 25 points each and last set 15 points.</li>
                        <li>At least 3 people from a team should serve and the same player cannot continue serving once it is broken.</li>
                        <li>Service must be done within 8 seconds of referee’s whistle, or else the serve will be passed, and one point is awarded to the opponent.</li>
                        <li>Net touch and center line cross will be considered as foul.</li>
                        <li>Referee’s decision is final and any appeal or argument against it will not be entertained.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Manasvi Surasani : 7032910997/p>
                </p>
   ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="WaterPolo">
            <![CDATA[
   <p><b>POINTS:-
                 <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1st place - 20 points
                 <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;2nd place - 12 points
                 <br>&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;3rd place - 8 points</b>
                </p>
                <p>RULES:-
                    <ul class="rules">
                    <li>The tournament is conducted on a knockout basis.</li>
                    <li>Each team shall consist of a maximum of thirteen players: eleven field players and two goalkeepers.</li>
                     <li>A team shall start the game with not more than seven players, one of whom shall be the goalkeeper and who shall wear the goalkeeper’s cap.</li>
                    <li>Five reserves may be used as substitutes and one reserve goalkeeper who may be used only as a substitute goalkeeper.</li>
                    <li>Rolling substitutes are allowed.</li>
                     <li>A team playing with less than seven players shall not be required to have a goalkeeper.</li>
                    <li>The match will consist of four quarters, each of length 6 minutes.</li>
                    <li>The captains shall be playing members of their respective teams and each shall be responsible for the good conduct and discipline of his team.</li>
                    <li>If a tie exists at the end of 24 minutes of play, the teams shall shoot penalty shots to determine which team won. Each team shall nominate five players and a goalkeeper who will participate in the penalty shoot-out. The team shall shoot five penalty shots at the goal of the other team, alternating shots.</li>
                    <li>If a tie exists after each team has taken five shots, then the teams shall take sets of alternate shots until one team scores and the other does not.</li>
                    <li>At any time in the game, a player may be substituted by leaving the field of play at the re-entry area nearest to the player’s own goal line. The substitute may enter the field of play from the re-entry area as soon as the player has visibly risen to the surface of the water within the re-entry area. </li>
                    <li>If a goalkeeper is substituted it must only be by the substitute goalkeeper.</li>
                    <li>A substitute shall be ready to replace a player without delay. If the substitute is not ready, the game shall continue without the substitute and, at any time, the substitute may then enter the field of play from the re-entry area nearest to the substitute’s own goal line.</li>

                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>CONTACT :
                    <p>Esun Selvam: 9940222566</p>
                </p>
   ]]>
    </string>


</resources>
